Zoe: Since I've been working with
children with autism, as it's mainly
been within school settings, I've worked
alongside educational psychologists,
staff within the school, speech and
language therapists, occupational
therapists, learning support assistance.
Phil: .So there's teaching assistants,
or as we call them in our institution,
educational assistants and the class
teacher for the education purposes,
and then the wider team around our
learners involve speech and language
therapists, occupational therapists,
play therapists and school counselors.
And also we work very closely
with our team of positive
behavior support practitioners.
Ellen: We've got the educational
assistance, so they will offer
support by coming into the classroom
and working with the students to
make sure that they stay on top.
Then we've got the occupational health,
we've got speech and language therapists,
so they will more kind of talk about how
to help the students communicate different
ways that we can help them as well.
Zoe T: The people who've been most
helpful to me have been other parents
and relationship development intervention
consultants, so RDI consultants,
because parents are the ones that know
what it's like to live with autism.
And relationship development
intervention consultants is
specifically our family consultant.
She has helped me to understand
autism in a way that nobody else has
ever enabled me to understand it.
I feel like I really
understand it properly.
Kerry: At school we're very lucky to
have speech and language therapists.
We've got occupational therapists.
We also have positive
behavior support team.
I've also worked with community access
and residential support for some of
our learners who might spend once
a week or maybe a little bit longer
at a temporary residency and then
go home for the rest of the time.
I've worked on the other side before
I came here, I've worked with SENCOs
and the Chesire East autism team.
I've worked alongside psychiatrists
and psychologists and nurses
and doctors on many different
levels, so like continence nurses,